Guide to the Actors' Fund of America Records WAG.036
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: General Files, 1881-2013; 184172
  - Programs (souvenir), 1923-1941; 184216 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Programs (souvenir), Belasco Theater, The Accused, 1925; 184215 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Programs (souvenir), Century Theater, Shakespeare's Plays, 1921; 184214 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Publicity, 1980, 1983; 184213 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Publicity: Clippings, undated; 184212 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Publicity: Clippings, 1881; 184211 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Publicity: Clippings, 1912-1919; 184210 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Publicity: Clippings, 1920-1929; 184209 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Publicity: Clippings, 1930-1939; 184208 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Publicity: Clippings, 1940-1949; 184207 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Publicity: Clippings, 1950-1959; 184206 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Publicity: Clippings, 1960-1969; 184205 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Publicity: Clippings, 1970-1979; 184204 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Publicity: Clippings, 1980-1988; 184203 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Publicity: Clippings, 1989; 184202 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Radio City Music Hall, 1985; 184201 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - RAI Corporation (Radiotelevisione Italiana), 1986; 184200 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Requests, 1981-1984; 184199 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Roosevelt, President Franklin D.: Telegram from, 1941; 184198 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - San Quentin Drama Group, 1961; 184197 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Shaw, Rosette, undated, 1961, 1975; 184196 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Sponder, Wanda, 1933-1947, 2001; 184195 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Survival Jobs Program: Reception, 1989; 184194 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Swayd, Lester, 1929-1946; 184193 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Theatre Development Fund, 1989; 184192 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Theatre Historical Society, 1976; 184191 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Theatre in America, 1986; 184190 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Tomkins, Don, 1926-1949, 1963-1968; 184189 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Tomkins, Don: Clippings, 1920-1969; 184188 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Tomkins, Don: Programs, 1930-1949, 1960-1969; 184187 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Tomkins, Don: Wildcat Scrapbook: Correspondence (from Joan Crawford and others), 1960-1977; 184186 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Tomkins, Don: Wildcat Scrapbook: Programs and Printed Material, undated, 1960-1961; 184185 (Box 11, Folder 13a)
  - Treasurers Club of America, 1940; 184184 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - United Way, 1991; 184183 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Wasowski, Andy: "On Next to Closing", 1981; 184182 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Weekly Relief List: Non-Actors, 1968; 184181 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Western Council, 1984-1985; 184180 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Western Council, 1986-1988; 184179 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Western Council, 1989; 184178 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Western Council: Committee Meetings, 1984-1985, 1989; 184177 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Western Council: Committee Members, 1984-1986; 184176 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Western Council: Dissolution and Re-Appointment, 1985-1986; 184175 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Williams, Percy, 1978, 1985; 184174 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Wolfington, Iggie, 1977-1980; 184173 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Series IV: Actors Work Program, 1986-1999; 184137
  - Advisory Board, 1989-1995; 184171 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Board of Directors, 1990-1992; 184170 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Board of Directors: Correspondence, 1990-1995; 184169 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Board of Directors: Meetings, 1989; 184168 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Board of Directors: Meetings, 1990; 184167 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Board of Directors: Meetings, 1991; 184166 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Board of Directors: Meetings, 1992; 184165 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Board of Directors: Meetings, 1993; 184164 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Board of Directors: Meetings, 1994; 184163 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Board of Directors: Meetings (includes audio tapes), 1995; 184162 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Budgets, 1989-1992; 184161 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Budgets, 1993-1996; 184160 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Certificate of Incorporation, 1987; 184159 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1987-1993; 184158 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1998-1999; 184157 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Actors' Equity Association, 1989-1993, 1996; 184156 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, New York City Department of Aging, 1994; 184155 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Screen Actors' Guild, 1992-1994; 184154 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Counseling Department: Report, 1992; 184153 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Finances, 1986-1988; 184152 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Flyers, undated, 1990; 184151 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Hornet Foundation, 1987-1991; 184150 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Individual Contributors, 1997-1998; 184149 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - New York City Department of Employment, 1989-1993; 184148 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - New York City Department of Employment: Contractual Agreements, 1990; 184147 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - New York City Department of Employment: Project Operating Plan, 1989; 184146 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Newsletters, 1989-2003; 184145 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Pilot Project: Reports, undated, 1987; 184144 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Regional Education Center, undated, 1990-1992; 184143 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Regional Education Center: Educational Grants, 1990-1992; 184142 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Regional Education Center: Finances, 1989-1991; 184141 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Regional Education Center: Reports, 1992; 184140 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Reports, Miscellaneous, 1990, 1997-1998; 184139 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Willard Swire Scholarship Committee, 1993; 184138 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Series V: Fundraising Activities, 1886-2002; 183462
  - Subseries V:A: Auctions and Bazaars, 1971-1989., 184112
    - Auction, 1972-1973; 184136 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Auction, 1972-1973; 184135 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Auction: Correspondence from Donors (includes Katharine Hepburn, James Cagney, Emlyn Williams, Sidney Kingsley, George Cukor, Dorothy Stickney, Katherine Cornell, Judith Anderson, Cyril Ritchard, Anita Loos, and Zero Mostel), 1972-1973; 184134 (Box 12, Folder 27, Box Shared Tamiment 042)
    - Auction: Moss Hart, "Once in a Lifetime" Manuscript, Authentication, etc., 1973; 184133 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Auction: Sponsors (includes correspondence from Nelson A. Rockefeller and Patricia Nixon), 1972-1973; 184132 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Auction, 1977; 184131 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Auction: "Going Once Twice Sold!", 346630 (Box 12, Folder 30A)
    - Auction: Howard Hawley Campaign, 1989; 184130 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Auction: NYPL Theatre Collection, Catalog, Oct 7, 1971; 184129 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Auction: Sotheby, Early American Furniture, 1978; 184128 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Bazaar, 1974; 184127 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Bazaar, 1977-1978; 184126 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Bazaar, 1980; 184125 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Bazaar: Annie, Cast Christmas Party, 1978; 184124 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Bazaar: Anniversary, 1978; 184123 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Bazaar: Clippings, 1977-1978; 184122 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Bazaar: Closing, 1979; 184121 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Bazaar Committee, 1977-1979; 184120 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Bazaar: Correspondence, 1975, 1978-1979; 184119 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Bazaar: Donations and Gifts, undated, 1976-1980; 184118 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Bazaar: Memorabilia: Peter Pan Collection, 1978-1979; 184117 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Bazaar: Minskoff Theatre, 1978; 184116 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Bazaar: Springtime, 1976; 184115 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Bazaar: Springtime: Correspondence, 1976; 184114 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Bazaar West (Manhattan Plaza), 1977; 184113 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Subseries V:B: Benefits and Fairs, 1886-2002., 183609
    - Benefit Program (Boston), 1886; 184111 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Benefit Program: Fair, 1892; 184110 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Benefit Program, 1905; 184109 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Benefit Program: Fair, 1907; 184108 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Benefit Program: Fair, 1910; 184107 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Benefit Program: Fair, 1912; 184106 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Benefit Program, 1913; 184105 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Benefit Program, 1914; 184104 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Benefit Program, Actors' Fund Day, 1914; 184103 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Benefit Program, 1915; 184102 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Benefit Program, 1916; 184101 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Benefit Program, 1917; 184100 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Benefit Program: Fair, 1917; 184099 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Benefit Program, 1918; 184098 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Benefit Program, 1919; 184097 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Benefit Program, 1920; 184096 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Benefit Program (I), 1921; 184095 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Benefit Program (II), 1921; 184094 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Benefit Program, 1923; 184093 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Benefit Program, 1924; 184092 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Benefit Program, 1925; 184091 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Benefit Program, 1926; 184090 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Benefit Program, 1927; 184089 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Benefit Program: British Commission, 1927; 184088 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Benefit Program, 1928; 184087 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Benefit Program, 1929; 184086 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Benefit Program, 1931; 184085 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Benefit Program, 1933; 184084 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Benefit Program, 1934; 184083 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Benefit Program, 1936; 184082 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Benefit Program, 1939; 184081 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Benefit Program, 1940; 184080 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Benefit Program, 1941; 184079 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Benefit Program, 1942; 184078 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Benefit Program, 1943; 184077 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Benefit Program, 1944; 184076 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Special Performances: Benefit Programs (partial), 1944-1949; 184075 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Benefit Program, 1947; 184074 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Benefit Program, 1948; 184073 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Song of Norway, Jan 5, 1948; 184072 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Star Spangled Carnival, Hospitalized Veterans Music Service, Nov 29, 1948; 184071 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Benefit Program, 1950; 184070 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Special Performances: Benefit Programs (partial), 1951-1959; 184069 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Richard III, Mar 11, 1956; 184068 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Thurber Carnival, May 1, 1960; 184067 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Toys in the Attic, May 9, 1960; 184066 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Best Man, Jun 12, 1960; 184065 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Bye Bye Birdie, Jun 19, 1960; 184064 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - World of Suzie Wong, Aug 20, 1960; 184063 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - My Fair Lady, Aug 28, 1960; 184062 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Duel of Angels, Sep 25, 1960; 184061 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Taste of Honey, Nov 20, 1960; 184060 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Flower Drum Song, Nov 27, 1960; 184059 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Hostage, Nov 27, 1960; 184058 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - West Side Story, Nov 27, 1960; 184057 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - La Plume Da Ma Tante, Dec 11, 1960; 184056 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Evening with Mike Nichols and Elaine May, Dec 18, 1960; 184055 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - All the Way Home, Jan 1, 1961; 184054 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Five Finger Exercise, Jan 8, 1961; 184053 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Miracle Worker, Jan 8, 1961; 184052 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Period of Adjustment, Jan 15, 1961; 184051 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Advise and Consent, Jan 22, 1961; 184050 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Becket, Jan 29, 1961; 184049 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Invitation to a March, Feb 5, 1961; 184048 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Critics' Choice, Feb 12, 1961; 184047 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Irma Le Douce, Feb 19, 1961; 184046 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Show Girl, Feb 26, 1961; 184045 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - Unsinkable Molly Brown, Mar 5, 1961; 184044 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - Wildcat, Mar 12, 1961; 184043 (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - Under the Yum Yum Tree, Mar 19, 1961; 184042 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - Rhinoceros, Mar 26, 1961; 184041 (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - Camelot, Apr 9, 1961; 184040 (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - Tenderloin, Apr 22, 1961; 184039 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - Do Re Mi, Apr 30, 1961; 184038 (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - American Dream, May 1, 1961; 184037 (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - Come Blow Your Horn, May 7, 1961; 184036 (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - Mary, Mary, May 14, 1961; 184035 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - Devil's Advocate, May 18, 1961; 184034 (Box 14, Folder 52)
    - Big Fish, Little Fish, May 21, 1961; 184033 (Box 14, Folder 53)
    - Golden Hind, May 21, 1961; 184032 (Box 14, Folder 54)
    - Far Country, Jun 4, 1941; 184031 (Box 14, Folder 55)
    - Happiest Girl in the World, Jun 11, 1961; 184030 (Box 14, Folder 56)
    - Majority of One, Jun 18, 1961; 184029 (Box 14, Folder 57)
    - Sound of Music, Jun 18, 1961; 184028 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Music Man, Aug 27, 1961; 184027 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Carnival, Oct 15, 1961; 184026 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Bye Bye Birdie, Oct 29, 1961; 184025 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Purlie Victorious, Nov 5, 1961; 184024 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Sound of Music, Nov 16, 1961; 184023 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Caretaker, Nov 19, 1961; 184022 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - From the Second City, Nov 26, 1961; 184021 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Andersonville Trial, Nov 27, 1961; 184020 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Evening with Yues Montand, Dec 3, 1961; 184019 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - How to Succeed in Business without Really Trying, Dec 10, 1961; 184018 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Milk and Honey, Dec 17, 1961; 184017 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Fiorello, Jan 3, 1962; 184016 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Sail Away, Jan 7, 1962; 184015 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Shot in the Dark, Jan 14, 1962; 184014 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Best Man, Jan 14, 1962; 184013 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Complaisant Lover, Jan 28, 1962; 184012 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Gay Life, Feb 4, 1962; 184011 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Gideon, Feb 11, 1962; 184010 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Man for All Seasons, Feb 18, 1962; 184009 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Write Me a Murder, Mar 4, 1962; 184008 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Night of the Iguana, Mar 11, 1962; 184007 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Take Her, She's Mine, Mar 18, 1962; 184006 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Passage to India, Mar 25, 1962; 184005 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - No Strings, Apr 15, 1962; 184004 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - All American, May 20, 1962; 184003 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - I Can Get It for You Wholesale, May 29, 1962; 184002 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Subways Are for Sleeping, Jun 3, 1962; 184001 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Thousand Clowns, Jun 17, 1962; 184000 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Moon Is Blue, Jun 18, 1962; 183999 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum, Sep 23, 1962; 183998 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Stop the World, I Want to Get Off, Nov 18, 1962; 183997 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Seidman and Son, Nov 25, 1962; 183996 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - How to Succeed in Business without Really Trying, Dec 2, 1962; 183995 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Mary, Mary, Dec 2, 1962; 183994 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Beyond the Fringe, Dec 9, 1962; 183993 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Shot in the Dark, Dec 19, 1962; 183992 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf?, Jan 20, 1963; 183991 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Calculated Risk, Feb 3, 1963; 183990 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Never Too Late, Feb 10, 1963; 183989 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Lord Pengo, Feb 17, 1963; 183988 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Tchin-Tchin, Mar 3, 1963; 183987 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - School for Scandal, Mar 10, 1963; 183986 (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Oliver!, Mar 17, 1963; 183985 (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Come Blow Your Horn, Apr 1, 1963; 183984 (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - Little Me, Apr 7, 1963; 183983 (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - Ages of Man, Apr 14, 1963; 183982 (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Photo Finish, May 12, 1963; 183981 (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - How to Succeed in Business without Really Trying, Jul 14, 1963; 183980 (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - Under the Yum Yum Tree, Aug 4, 1963; 183979 (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - Enter Laughing, Sep 8, 1963; 183978 (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - She Loves Me, Sep 22, 1963; 183977 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Man for All Seasons, Oct 27, 1963; 183976 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Stop the World, I Want to Get Off, Nov 3, 1963; 183975 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Private Ear & the Public Eye, Nov 17, 1963; 183974 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - How to Succeed in Business without Really Trying, Dec 8, 1963; 183973 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Case of Libel, Dec 15, 1963; 183972 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Camelot, Dec 29, 1963; 183971 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Barefoot in the Park, Jan 5, 1964; 183970 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Here's Love, Jan 12, 1964; 183969 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Marathon, Jan 19, 1964; 183968 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Ballad of the Sad Café, Jan 26, 1964; 183967 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Nobody Loves an Albatross, Feb 2, 1964; 183966 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Luther, Feb 9, 1964; 183965 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - 110 in the Shade, Feb 16, 1964; 183964 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Girl Who Came to Supper, Feb 23, 1964; 183963 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Chinese Prime Minister, Mar 1, 1964; 183962 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Dylan, Mar 8, 1964; 183961 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Any Wednesday, Apr 12, 1964; 183960 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Hello, Dolly!, Apr 16, 1964; 183959 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - What Makes Sammy Run?, Apr 19, 1964; 183958 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Funny Girl, May 3, 1964; 183957 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf, May 10, 1964; 183956 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Hamlet, May 17, 1964; 183955 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - High Spirits, Jun 14, 1964; 183954 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - World of Kurt Weill in Song, Jun 28, 1964; 183953 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Subject Was Roses, Jul 19, 1964; 183952 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Fade Out- Fade In, Aug 9, 1964; 183951 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Baby Want a Kiss, Aug 16, 1964; 183950 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Three Sisters, Sep 20, 1964; 183949 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Oh What a Lovely War, Jan 3, 1965; 183948 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Owl and the Pussycat, Jan 17, 1965; 183947 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Luv, Jan 24, 1965; 183946 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Poor Richard, Jan 31, 1965; 183945 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Golden Boy, Feb 7, 1965; 183944 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Barefoot in the Park, Feb 14, 1965; 183943 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Committee, Feb 21, 1965; 183942 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Barefoot in the Park, Feb 28, 1965; 183941 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Fiddler on the Roof, Mar 7, 1965; 183940 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - I Had a Ball, Mar 18, 1965; 183939 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Do I Hear a Waltz?, May 2, 1965; 183938 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Roar of the Greasepaint- the Smell of the Crowd, May 16, 1965; 183937 (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Glass Menagerie, Jun 6, 1965; 183936 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Baker Street, May 23, 1965; 183935 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Bernard Shaw Story, Aug 15, 1965; 183934 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Odd Couple, Sep 12, 1965; 183933 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Half a Sixpence, Sep 26, 1965; 183932 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Hello, Dolly!, Oct 17, 1965; 183931 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Chips with Everything, Nov 10, 1965; 183930 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Generation, Nov 28, 1965; 183929 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Funny Girl, Dec 19, 1965; 183928 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - You Can't Take It with You, Jan 9, 1966; 183927 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - On a Clear Day You Can See Forever, Jan 30, 1966; 183926 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Zulu and the Zayda, Feb 13, 1966; 183925 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Skyscraper, Feb 20, 1966; 183924 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Hostile Witness, Mar 13, 1966; 183923 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Royal Hunt of the Sun, Mar 20, 1966; 183922 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Marat/De Sade, Mar 27, 1966; 183921 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Cactus Flower, Apr 3, 1966; 183920 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Philadelphia, Here I Come, Apr 10, 1966; 183919 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Wait Until Dark, Apr 17, 1966; 183918 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Sweet Charity, Apr 24, 1966; 183917 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Wait a Minim!, May 8, 1966; 183916 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Dylan, May 9, 1966; 183915 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Impossible Years, May 22, 1966; 183914 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Odd Couple, Jul 17, 1966; 183913 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Show Boat, Aug 28, 1966; 183912 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Man of LaMancha, Sep 11, 1966; 183911 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Fiddler on the Roof, Sep 25, 1966; 183910 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Mame, Oct 16, 1966; 183909 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Delicate Balance, May 27, 1966; 183908 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Apple Tree, Jan 15, 1967; 183907 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Cabaret, Jan 22, 1967; 183906 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Star Spangled Girl, Mar 5, 1967; 183905 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - At the Drop of Another Hat, Apr 9, 1967; 183904 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Homecoming, Apr 16, 1967; 183903 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Fiddler on the Roof, Apr 23, 1967; 183902 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Black Comedy, Apr 30, 1967; 183901 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Mary, Mary, May 6, 1967; 183900 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - You Know I Can't Hear You When the Water's Running, May 21, 1967; 183899 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Don't Drink the Water, Jun 4, 1967; 183898 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - South Pacific, Aug 27, 1967; 183897 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Man of LaMancha, Sep 10, 1967; 183896 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Mame, Oct 22, 1967; 183895 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Illy a Darling, Nov 5, 1967; 183894 (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - I Do, I Do, Dec 3, 1967; 183893 (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - There's a Girl in My Soup, Dec 17, 1967; 183892 (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - Brief Lines, Jan 7, 1968; 183891 (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Pantagleize, Jan 14, 1968; 183890 (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - More Stately Mansions, Jan 21, 1968; 183889 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - How Now, Don Jones, Mar 10, 1968; 183888 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Happy Time, Mar 17, 1968; 183887 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Rosencrantz and Guildenstern Are Dead, Mar 24, 1968; 183886 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Hello, Dolly!, Mar 31, 1968; 183885 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Fiddler on the Roof, Apr 3, 1968; 183884 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Cabaret Cancelled Performance, Apr 7, 1968; 183883 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Price, May 5, 1968; 183882 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Prime of Miss Jean Brodie, May 12, 1968; 183881 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Plaza Suite, Jul 21, 1968; 183880 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - West Side Story, Aug 25, 1968; 183879 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - George M, Oct 13, 1968; 183878 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Lovers, Oct 27, 1968; 183877 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Marlene Dietrich, Nov 24, 1968; 183876 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Hair, Dec 7, 1968; 183875 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Show- Off, Dec 15, 1968; 183874 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Great White Hope, Jan 5, 1969; 183873 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Man in the Glass Bottom, Jan 19, 1969; 183872 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Celebration, Feb 23, 1969; 183871 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Zorba, Mar 9, 1969; 183870 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Hadrian VII, Mar 16, 1969; 183869 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Forty Carats, Mar 23, 1969; 183868 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Promises, Promises, Mar 30, 1969; 183867 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Play It Again, Sam, Apr 6, 1969; 183866 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Jimmy Shine, Apr 13, 1969; 183865 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Canterbury Tales, Apr 27, 1969; 183864 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Front Page, Jun 29, 1969; 183863 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Oklahoma!, Aug 24, 1969; 183862 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - 1776, Oct 5, 1969; 183861 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Butterflies Are Free, Jan 18, 1970; 183860 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Hair, Feb 2, 1970; 183859 (Box 18, Folder 31)